What is the truth? Do you kill people?
No.
No more lies. please.
No more lies.
My American friend
picked up some chatter.
Rodin. price point agreed.
Jackal en route.
We have intelligence that a contract's
been taken out on your life.
Who's taken out this contract?
We don't have that information. sir.
Norman definitely knew we were coming.
Who exactly is this Norman Stowe?
The sniper took the
weapon he used to kill
Fest with him.
and this is how he did It.
All thanks to Norman Stowe.
Norman. I need an address.
I'll talk to my man.
I want you to see this.
Tell me everything I need to know.
The Jackal. Where is he now?
He should be in Tallinn.
You need to find
him and stay with him.
Hello.
You've taken 20 million
dollars from people
who are used to getting
what they paid for.
And they didn't pay you
to go rogue in Munich.
If I don't deliver.
if you don't deliver.
It will take extreme measures.
You do not want to make
enemies of these people.
They're more powerful
than you know.
If you don't believe me.
just ask Norman Stowe.
Nobody wants you to
succeed more than me.
I'm a huge admirer of your work.
Some flowers never get
to bloom and see the day.
Some flowers are content
to wish their lives away.
Some may rise and some may fall.
But only you may
ever see me true.
So only you can tell
that this is who I am.
This is who I am.
I'll be staying in
Tallinn until delivery.
So if you need anything.
you can call me.
My phone's secure.
A babysitter.
Anything.
You alright?
A little Bianca one week.
He tried to kill my daughter.
Fair point.
Outside.
Go on.
Off you fuck.
No one comes in. understood?
Where's Norman?
Fuck you.
Trust me when I say I will find
Norman and I will kill him myself.
She ain't fucking about.
We're not police.
We don't need arrest warrants.
She finds him.
she's gonna kill him.
Tell us what we need to know.
And one.
we don't kill Norman.
Two.
instead of you going
to prison for life.
the two of you do.
what. five years Max?
Nice comfy prison.
You do five standing on your head.
Larry.
And three.
you get to go home to Bury Allison.
Emma.
and say your goodbyes.
So you're gonna speak to me?
No.
Fuck you.
Thank you.
It was only made possible
by a very fine instrument.
Merely by a maestro.
Yeah. the best.
Before I get to that.
um.
I've got a question for you. Norman.
Shoot.
What's been going on with you?
What do you mean?
I mean.
have you experienced anything
unusual recently?
You could say unusual.
Yeah. how did you know?
What exactly?
I need to know before
we can go any further.
I was on a business trip.
Abroad.
Some visitors showed up.
They weren't invited and
they weren't bringing flowers.
Who were they?
I didn't stop to chat.
Let's just say I gave them a wee
Belfast welcome and I got out of there.
Ryan. you're 100% secure now.
100%.
You know I don't like risks.
You know I do.
I don't either.
Distance to the target is 75 metres.
I'D like you to get that snug.
Yeah. unfortunately.
It's my only option.
What are the obstacles?
A metal detector
and an ultra-sensitive
scanner.
but I've got an idea for that.
When do you need It?
Well. the job's in five days.
There's a problem?
Name your price. old man.
It's not about the money.
The visitors I mentioned.
I got clipped in the arm.
I can't even wipe my arse properly.
I'm on my own.
I won't make a deadline.
Is there anyone that can help you?
No one I trust.
Would you trust me?
You won't kill him?
Is that a guarantee?
Cast iron.
Where is he. Larry?
Where's Norman?
Budapest.
Budapest?
What's the address?
He picked me up at the airport.
How long did It take for you to
get from the airport to his place?
I don't know. about an hour.
It was out of town.
Was It a village? A suburb?
What did It look like?
There was a coffee shop at
the corner of Norman Street.
There were stables
at the back with horses.
What sort of place has he got?
A house? An apartment?
It's not a house.
It's a big white building.
With a gate and a yard.
That's all I know.
That is all I know!
How did you find out where I live?
Norman told me.
How did Norman know?
Norman moves in
different circles than me.
He can find stuff out.
So. one of these guys
is a dirty little mole.
Yep.
Just give me a minute.
I have an update on Alexander Duggan.
Uh-huh?
He was a loner.
Details freak.
Pure sniper material.
His unit specialized in
eliminating Taliban leaders.
Killed a lot of people.
But they were taken out by
an IED in Helmand in 2013.
So. Duggan is dead.
Yep.
Was his body recovered?
I assume so. but I can check.
Yep.
Bit of a weird
atmosphere in the office.
Paranoia levels are
going through the roof.
Can you get a photograph
of Duggan while you're at It?
Yep. Copy that.
Great.
I've widened the parameters to make It
a 90 minute radius from the airport.
He described It as a big white
building with a gate and a yard.
Coffee shop on the
corner of the street.
Stables at the back.
How long until we
have a precise location?
It's a little vague.
Might take a while.
Well. get a move on.
An assassin's on the run.
Right. No pressure then.
You haven't given
me much to work with.
The thinker or the stinker?
Shit.
Rodan is UDC.
The Jackal's next target.
Well.
that certainly raises the stakes.
And he's been pissing
off a lot of powerful people.
I assume you shared this with Isabel.
You said keep the circle tight.
He knows. We go way back.
Alright.
What's your next step?
I need to find Norman Stoke.
And we think we have a
rough idea of where Norman is.
Where?
I get It.
But I'm assuming as soon
as you have a precise location
you'll want to move
quickly and pick him up.
Yeah. that's the plan.
For which you'll need
authorization and logistical support.
Apart from Isabel. the only person
who can do that under the radar is me.
If I'm to help.
I need the details. Where is he?
Somewhere near Budapest.
We don't know where exactly.
but as soon as we do. we can move.
I'll start making arrangements.
When you're ready to roll.
let me know.
Yeah. in your own time.
Been standing here
for the past 20 minutes.
I know. You're taller than I imagined.
I'm slimmer.
Okay. where the fuck are you?
I'll go to the southeast
corner of the square.
I'll pick you up.
Ugh.
What's the update?
We've got 17 possible locations
within 90 minutes of the airport.
Yeah. that's not gonna work.
Take It down to 60.
A 60 minute radius gives you
11 locations that fit your criteria.
Still too many.
Anything else to narrow It down?
Nope.
All right. We'll see what
else we can come up with.
Fingers crossed. eh?
The house is the next left.
Hi. Do you have any idea how
much damage you're causing?
Well. straight in. I'm just here to
talk to my husband and my child.
Can you call them. please?
A good mother
wouldn't have to be here.
You do not want me to comment on you.
No one's trying to speak to you.
I'm trying to talk to my
husband and my child.
About deal with this. really?
Try and think of It from her
point of view for one second.
Why do I need to look
at It from her point of view
when I'm coming to speak
to you and see my child?
What happened last night
might be normal to you.
but for the rest of us.
It's really fucking scary.
Okay. Jasmine. is she there?
What's going on?
She's fine. She's with the boys.
They've been really great with her.
So is Angela.
Are you coming home?
Or are you staying here
with your fucking ex-wife?
Hmm?
Okay.
From the start.
you've been really upfront
with me about how much you
love your job and how
important It is to you. okay?
But last night.
you brought danger into our home.
Between that knife being
held at my daughter's neck
and that gun you had
pointed in her direction.
Jasmine could have
been fucking killed.
She wasn't. I dealt with It.
She said you tortured the man.
He had information
and I needed to get It from him.
I don't even want
to know what you're
saying with that statement.
but either way.
Jesus Christ. It's not really
ideal mothering. is It. Bianca?
I'm trying. Paul. I have a job to do.
We've all got jobs to do.
It's just that some of us understand
that in families.
you've got to make compromises.
In your job. you can
be late for a conference or bring
in a paper late and It's just my job.
If I'm not where they
tell me to be at the
exact time that they
tell me to be there.
then someone dies.
Do you understand?
I don't recognize you anymore.
What are the limitations?
Right. so the main
limitation is going to be size.
so the action and bolts should
be no bulkier than about that.
Do you need a trigger guard?
No. but I was wondering
if I could get the trigger
removable like the last one so that
I can attach It just before firing.
Why? Because the
whole mechanism
needs to fit into that.
Oh. yes.
That's nice.
That's very clever. Thank you.
I mentioned the scanner and I think
that's going to be pretty sensitive.
Fracture boots. sir.
They're made of
plastic and polymer.
They'll get through
the scanner easy.
But the firing mechanism
and the barrel.
they're going to show up.
Sir. I was wondering about
the whole thing plastic.
You can't make a
barrel out of plastic.
It doesn't matter if It's
machined or 3D printed.
But we could try
a low round count
disposable barrel made
from lightweight alloy.
How many rounds will that give me?
Usually It'll be a
one shot throw away.
but with a maestro like me.
you could get up to eight shots.
Seven for sure.
All right. now that'll be plenty.
Can I get a silencer as well?
We could print the suppressor core.
It would confuse the
scanner operators.
What are we thinking time-wise?
It's going to take us four or five
hours to write the program and then
another ten hours to print.
Do you have time for that?
If we start now. yeah.
All right. well. I'm off for a shite.
a char. and a smoke.
Nell. be ready.
If Charles finds out I'm here.
we're in big trouble.
Are you sure you can fix It?
Yes. don't worry.
But Nuri. listen to me.
If you don't believe anything I say.
why do you want me to fix It?
But please. listen to me.
Okay?
Whatever you want.
Yeah.
All right.
Shall we get started?
Let us.
G-9-M-8-2.
Yeah.
M-1-4-0.
S-1-4.
Once the print is started.
It'll take ten. twelve hours.
Ugh.
Ah.
Pain medication.
Yeah. yeah.
Shall we have a wee drop?
No. I'm good. thank you.
Ah. you might change your mind.
Cheers.
Go on. then.
Well done.
Oh.
Jeez.
look at these glasses.
This place could do
with a woman's touch.
Do you ever have a wife?
A wife? Yeah.
Ah. Well. once.
Nearly.
She's a great woman.
Great cook. Great in bed.
It's great company.
Yeah. but sure. in our game.
you can't have a wife.
You think?
A hundred percent. Especially
if you fall in love with them.
What I was all was fall in love.
Fucking nightmare.
I'm a hopeless romantic.
Is that what that trip abroad was?
Was that a romantic thing?
No. no. I was business.
A client with
specialist needs. Like you.
Where'D you go?
Client.
Confidentiality.
Where'D you go?
Silence makes me a bit nervous.
It was Belarus.
Right.
Who came calling for you in Belarus.
Norman?
Russians?
They had English accents.
Did you see them?
I bet you shot me.
Or saw her all right then.
She's a woman. Black woman.
She had a Glock 17.
A black. armed British woman.
In Belarus.
You lied to me. old man.
I'm not lying to you.
I'm telling you all about It.
How'D you get away from an
MI6 snatched squad. Norman?
I had a bit of help.
Yeah. I got a tip off.
They were on their way. Who from?
There was no number.
It was just a message.
I said. clear right now.
You're an artist. my friend.
And you've always been discreet.
But if that changes...
Yeah.
I've got good news.
We think we've found
Norman's location.
It fits all the parameters
of an abandoned factory
in a place called Lawrencey.
Are you sure?
As sure as we can be.
Large white building.
56 minutes from Budapest airport.
By now It's our best shot.
Oh. see.
We might have a location.
Do we have authorization?
So It is Budapest?
Yeah.
It's Budapest.
I'll inform the Hungarians
that we're going to be
operating on their turf.
When you get to the airport.
I'll get the authorization.
If you need anything else.
give me a call.
Do you trust him?
Do you?
Try It on.
Yeah.
That's. uh. weirdly comfortable.
The scanner will pick
up the metal components.
Now that shouldn't
surprise the operator.
If he asks you to take It off.
you can tell him to fuck
off on medical grounds.
Show me how to build It.
That is a fucking work of art. Dallas.
So where's the nearest
place I can take this
for a spin without
attracting attention?
Well. top of the road. turn right.
left of the train tracks.
and keep going till
you get to some woods.
Right.
You can take my car.
I'm off to bed.
Oh.
Indy D's.
Couple of special ones in there. too.
Remember.
It's not gunmetal.
You'll get eight shots from It.
To be on the safe side.
keep the test firing to a minimum.
Welcome to Budapest.
The local time is 1.35.
We'D like to wish you
a safe Auburn journey.
There he is.
I just want you to know.
can I get the small one?
Two dozen. please.
Two dozen.
Hi.
Stranger.
Hola. mi amor.
You all right?
Yes.
You sure?
So I've been trying you.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
I just needed some time to think.
Okay.
Well. all good. I'm hoping.
Yeah. I think so.
When are you coming back?
Four or five days.
A week at most.
And then I promise you.
you are gonna be so
bored of me.
you're gonna be begging me to leave.
I just want everything to
be the way It used to be.
It's just up here on the left.
What are you doing?
He's great. Exhausting. but great.
I miss you both so much.
We miss you too.
But there's something we
need to discuss. Charles.
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
This certainly fits
Larry's description.
This is important. Charles.
I've gotta run now.
but I'll speak to you in a sec.
Okay. Love you. Bye.
Bye-bye.
I can't take It anymore. Álvaro.
He's lying.
Listen to me.
We can cut the power.
It's all arranged.
I just don't wanna
repeat your Belarus.
What do you wanna do?
It's your call.
All right. remember.
we need him alive.
Yeah?
You got visitors.
One of them looks like
your friend from MI6.
Clean up and get out now.
Just make sure you clean up.
Hello. Norman.
I know you made the gun
that killed Manfred Fest.
You know fuck all.
And here you are.
making a new one already. Norman.
Is this for the Jackal as well?
I have the foggiest idea
what you're talking about.
Must be impossible
with just the one arm.
Um...
Oh. what's all this?
Did you have a little friend over.
Norman?
Well. that makes sense.
You're a pretty sad
specimen on your own. eh?
Fuck you.
Tell us who the Jackal is.
I have the foggiest idea
what you're talking about.
Oh. come on. Norman.
What's the Jackal's name?
I haven't the foggiest idea
what you're talking about.
Oh. I think you do. Norman.
We know the Jackal's been
contracted for another hit.
Makes sense he'D need
another bespoke weapon.
And after you did such a
good job with the last one.
well. if It was me. I'D be hurt if
you didn't ask me for the next one.
This is his.
Isn't It. Norman?
Huh?
The Jackal's here. isn't he?
Come on. let's get him in the car.
No. Wait.
The Jackal's been here.
His things are here.
So he'll be back.
Tell Lena and Tamash to
keep watch on the street.
Change of plan.
Lena. stay by the car.
Tamash. take your position.
Well. while we're waiting.
Norman.
you can tell me
how you got my home address.
Hmm?
Was It the same person that tipped
you off that we were in Belarus?
I haven't the fuckiest idea
what you're talking about.
Aren't you wondering who
tipped us off about you?
Huh?
It was Larry.
Yeah? That's right.
Man. It must be really
hard finding out that
It was your own
brother who sold you out.
And It must be even harder when
the person standing in front of you
is the one who made him
talk and is gonna put you
both in jail for the rest
of your fucking lives.
Shooter. flanking left.
Does anyone have eyes on?
Can you see him?
Negative.
You okay?
Yes. I hate the vest.
I woke up one morning
to know where I had gone.
Finally taken a step and
jumped right off the wall.
When you come to call on me
that's where my eyes are glazed.
I've been with the devil
in the devil's resting place.
I am loveless to say
It's the devil's taste.
I've been with the devil
in the devil's resting place.
Water won't clean.